there's one thing you should know about there's one thing you should know about me
I specialize in a very specific type of security subconscious
you're talking about
dreams Mr car has a job offer he would like
to discuss with you kind a work
placement not exactly we create the world of
dream we bring the subject into that dream we bring the subject into that dream
and they fill it with their dream and they fill it with their secrets
then you break can ins Ste it well it's not
strictly speaking legal
it's called
Inception I'm
ready I think found a way ready I think found a way home
and this last job that's how I get
there dreams feel real while we're in there dreams feel real while we're in them
it's only when we wake up that realize something was
actually
strange this your responsibility we strange this was your responsibility we are
not prepared for
this dreams
collapsing I have it under control
I'd hate to see out of
control you mustn't be afraid to dream a little bigger
darling